

### Technical Leader

180 Dinh Thon, 100000, Ha Noi, My Dinh I VN

in harry-duong 🖸 thedv91

Strong experience in Software development with diverse domains over 8 years: Healthcare, Insurance, E-Commerce, etc.

Skilled in React, React Native, NodeJS, DevOps, ECMAScript, Solution Architecture, Technical Leadership and Agile Scrum

Working as Fullstack developer and Techincal Leader in different projects

Interested in research and study new technology and best-practice to optimize code quality

Able to approach and apply new technology into projects



#### **WORK EXPERIENCE (3)**

Technical Leader at NTQ Solution JSC July 2019- Current

♦ https://ntq.com.vn

Outsourcing company

- Build multi-project with NodeJS & React JS using GraphQL
- Develop Healthcare, Insurance, E-Commerce projects
- Optimize Google SEO
- Build Core Starterkit for NodeJS, ReactJS, React Native
- Build infrastructure, Auto deploy, high availability
- Performance test, load test, soak test and stress testing
- Code review
- Support bidding process

Outsourcing company

- Develop multi-project with ReactJS
- Develop RESTFul API with Laravel, NodeJS
- Technical Training
- Build Core Starterkit for NodeJS, ReactJS
- Build store with AngularJS
- Develop RESTFul API with Laravel
- Code Review

## **Developer** at ASINCO **December 2013- April 2015**

9

Product company to develop game for mobile

- Build backend management for CardGame with Laravel
- Mobile Game development with Unity

#### PROJECTS (4)

#### AIC (Technical Leader) January 2021- Current

http://sythcm.smartmedical.vn

medical typescript react nodejs socket.io graphql postgresql kafka kubernetes fhir

Medical device management and transfer system

- Centralized medical device management
- Understand medical equipment resources at affiliated medical facilities in real time
- Predict the condition of medical equipment and give alerts
- Process management of medical facilities
- Asset management and statistics of medical facilities
- Transfer of medical equipment between affiliated medical facilities in case of emergency
- Synchronize data from medical facilities to centralized health departments
- Control price fluctuations in the procurement of medical equipment by medical facilities

#### Sayang (Technical Leader) August 2020- Current

https://sayang-landing.ntq.solutions/



Sayang is Food Grocer centered e-commerce company in Singapore. The client wants to improve how market consumes food groceries by catering a platform to connect buyers and sellers within a community. This is a collective environment for engagement and exploration of food recipe videos and food grocery products. The system includes 1 mobile app, 1 web admin, 1 management web for Merchant

- Create post and share to the platform
- Merchant web business management

- Customer management
- Product and Order management

#### MBAL CMS (Technical Leader) May 2020- November 2020

https://www.mbageas.life/

insurance googlemaps page builder typescript react nodejs graphql postgresql

The Customer is a Vietnamese insurer who plans revamping its corporate website to refresh the brand and give it a stunning modern look. NTQ is requested to work on the new web design and consult on technology enhancements. Besides the user interface, NTQ also adds some new features including: Zalo/Facebook chat, online payment via VNPay and insurance cost calculation tool. The CMS system is also upgraded by using page builder to allow deep config. After completion, the new site is expected to improve the way end clients perceive the brand and to give them much better experience.

- Design a new website interface according to modern trends, support SEO-Marketing
- Integrate electronic payment gateway to allow users to pay online
- Develop tools to analyze costs and insurance package routes according to logic from customers
- Page builder allows admin to create new pages and intervene deeply in each element of the website UI
- Module to manage customer requests on the website which allows admin to view a list and respond to requests via the email server

#### FazzDoc (Technical Leader) March 2020- November 2020

https://www.facebook.com/fazzdoc

healthcare booking typescript react react native nodejs graphql postgresql elasticsearch

The health technology scene is very hot in Indonesia, but coming with complex business models. Moreover, booking a doctor is still very manual and hassle, done via telephone call or sometimes SMS, no guarantee. It is not very comfortable for patients. Our goal is to create Fazzdoc to be the 1st choice of users whenever they need to visit the doctor, plus book the doctor with the simplest and easiest way. Other than that, we need to supply the most complete and helpful information related to the doctor and hospital.

- Search and return doctors, medical facility and specialties matching the key word
- User books an appointment with a doctor.
- User and the hospital receive an email for successful booking
- When the initial booking is modified by the doctor/hospital and other doctors/timeslot are suggested, user can select one of the suggestion to update the booking
- User can cancel a booking as long as it is not Completed or Cancelled

#### **EDUCATION (1)**

**Bachelor Information Technology** at Hanoi University of industry **2009 - 2013** 



#### **AWARDS**

An award for best performance employees

# Employee of the year at NTQ Star 2019

An award for best performance employees

